flyordie.com 2018-10-17

# Legal Terms and Conditions

Welcome to FlyOrDie! By using FlyOrDie Games you agree to be bound by the following policies:

  * Site Rules
  * Privacy Policy
  * Terms of Service

* * *

## Site Rules

### Simply put: be nice, no cheating!

FlyOrDie is a friendly online community for those who love play! Please be on your best behavior as you play and interact with others. Failure to follow these rules will result in your account being closed.

### User interaction

Without respect toward others, no online community can function properly. Please be aware you are entering a community comprised of different age groups, heritages, races, social levels and educational backgrounds. There should be no abusive language, personal attacks, threats, or any other unkind behavior.

### Keep it clean

You may not post any offensive content on FlyOrDie including your user name, avatar, or personal description. You may not add any offensive comments, chat, or other content. The following behavior is strictly forbidden and can result in your being kicked or banned: cheating, using offensive/vulgar language, making personal attacks, spamming or advertising competitive websites, religious or political debate, intentionally pointless/distracting comments, disclosing other's personal data without consent, attempt to solicit account information from other players, and discussion of illegal activities (drugs, etc).

### No cheating

Any form of unsportsmanlike behavior will not be tolerated, FlyOrDie reserves the right to reset points to zero and/or ban your nickname for this offense. It includes artificially adjusting your rating, encouraging your opponent to leave the match, intentionally losing, accepting your opponent's behavior who is intentionally losing, using other's account, using more than one nicknames.

### Engines/programs

FlyOrDie members have the right to know if they are playing against a computer. Therefore FlyOrDie uses a system - including analysis of client computing environment - to detect suspected program use, which will be indicated at concerned player's nick with a small [!] icon. 

### Only one account

Members may only have ONE FlyOrDie.com account, unless explicitly allowed to have more. Members who create more than one account may have all accounts closed.

* * *

## Privacy Policy

### Who we are?

We are Solware Ltd, our address is 2100 Gödöllő, Kard utca 10, Hungary. We are the providers of the games found at flyordie.com (including all associated web-sites as: solware.com, flyordie.pl, flyordie.hu, startspiele.de, playcurling.com, sakk.hu, larkinor.com), all mobile games published by FlyOrDie, FlyOrDie games that can played through social media sites such as Facebook, or through other game providers.

By accessing any of our games, websites (referred to as the "FlyOrDie"), you agree to and accept this Privacy Policy. In the future, our practices may change, and if appropriate, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect the changes, and you agree that the information we collect will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect that information. We’ll post the updated version here and may contact you with notices concerning our Privacy Policy. In addition, we suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically, as it may be updated from time to time.

### Personal data we collect

FlyOrDie collects data to operate effectively and provide you the best experiences with our products. You provide some of this data directly, such as when you create a FlyOrDie account, participate in various activities on FlyOrDie such as chat, posting messages in the forum or contact us for support. 

We get some of it by recording how you interact with our products by, for example, using technologies like cookies, and using passive tracking technologies to log information such as IP address, browser type, pages visited, and website usage. 

There are basically three levels of users using FlyOrDie:

  1. simple visitors, or guests, who use the services without registering
  2. registered users
  3. subscribed members

  1. as a guest you do not provide any information directly to us, but we might collect some data while you interact with our services. The data we might collect from guests are IP address, browser types, time and date at each login. We use these data to analyse trends and create statistical records.
  2. as a registered user you have to provide some data when signing up. These include your email address, a username and password. These data are collected to protect your user account from unauthorized access. While using our game you also have the option to provide your age, gender and country, additionally you have the option to make these three data public to everyone who visits our site, or keep them private. These data are collected in order to make your experience more enjoyable   
Any message you send in the chat rooms, or post in the forum will be public and will be logged. Any match results, tournament results, forum posts are public, and cannot be deleted.   
Besides these data that you provide, we also collect some additional data when signing up for or while playing our games. These data include IP addresses, browser types, time and date of any interaction with our service, the amount of time you spend on our game, moderator notes, moderation history, your game results and statistics for each game you play. The aim to collect these data is fraud detection/prevention.
  3. as a subscribed member you also have to provide your billing address and name, which we need due to legal obligations. The data mentioned in section (b) refer to subscribed members as well.   
In case of credit card payments, your credit card information is not revealed to us, it is processed by our payment processing partners.

### How we use personal data 

We use these data to provide, protect and improve FlyOrDie's services and to make your experience more enjoyable. We also may use the data to communicate with you, for example, informing you about your account, security updates and product information.

### The lawful basis on which we process this information

In case of subscribed members your billing info is collected, processed and stored on legal obligation. The data collected by us is collected , processed and stored on our legitimate interests, in order to identify and prevent fraud, unauthorized access of your account, investigating suspicious activities.

### Storing this information

We keep your data for as long as your registration is active, or as it is required by law. Your account can be deleted if it is not used for a long time, or you can request it to be deleted. For details how your account can be deleted, please read the "Requesting to delete your personal data" section below.

### Who we share this information with

We do not share personally identifiable information that we have collected (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their own commercial or marketing purposes. 

### Children’s Privacy

The Site is designed for and directed at people 18 years of age or older. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 16. If a child under the age of 16 has submitted personally identifiable information online in contravention of these measures, account access will be terminated immediately and will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or other as required or allowed by law). If you become aware of any personal information we have collected from children under 16, please contact us at [dataprotection@flyordie.com](mailto:dataprotection@flyordie.com)

### Cookies

This site, like many others, uses small files called cookies to help us customise your experience. 

#### What are cookies?

Cookies are small text files that are stored by the browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Safari) on your computer or mobile phone. They allow websites to store things like user preferences. You can think of cookies as providing a ‘memory’ for the website, so that it can recognise you when you come back and respond appropriately.

#### How does FlyOrDie website use cookies?

A visit to a page on FlyOrDie website may generate the following types of cookie:

  * Site performance cookies
  * Anonymous analytics cookies
  * Registration cookies
  * Third party advertising cookies

#### Site performance cookies

This type of cookie remembers your preferences for tools found on the FlyOrDie’s website, so you don’t have to re-set them each time you visit. Examples include: your favourite games are remembered so you can start them easily.

#### Anonymous analytics cookies

Every time someone visits our website, software provided by another organisation generates an “anonymous analytics cookie”. These cookies can tell us whether or not you have visited the site before. Your browser will tell us if you have these cookies and, if you don’t, we generate new ones. This allows us to track how many individual users we have, and how often they visit the site. We use these data to gather statistics, for example, the number of visits to a page.

#### Registration cookies

When you register with FlyOrDie, we generate cookies that let us know whether you are signed in or not. Our servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with, and if you are allowed access to a particular service. 

#### Third party advertising cookies

Ads keep our content FREE for everyone. We use additional third-party advertising companies who serve ads to help keep content free.  These third party vendors, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites. The use of advertising cookies enables third party vendors and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. The companies that generate these cookies have their own privacy policies, and we have no access to read or write these cookies. These organizations may use their cookies to anonymously target advertising to you on other websites, based on your visit to FlyOrDie.

Third party vendors:

Google [Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) [Opt-out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)

Sovrn [Policy](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/)

Primis [Policy](https://www.primis.tech/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/primisPrivacyPolicy2018.pdf)

Chitika [Policy](https://chitika.com/privacy-policy/)

DistrictM [Policy](https://districtm.net/en/page/data-and-privacy-policy/)

#### Other third party cookies

On some pages of our website, other organisations may also set their own anonymous cookies. They do this to track the success of their application, or to customise the application for you. Because of how cookies work, our website cannot access these cookies, nor can the other organisation access the data in cookies we use on our website. For example, when you like one of our pages using a social-media like button (for example, Facebook) on FlyOrDie, the social network that has created the button will record that you have done this.

#### How do I turn cookies off?

All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can usually find these settings in the Options or Preferences menu of your browser. To understand these settings, you can use the Help option in your browser for more details. 

You can find out how to decline targeting and behavioural advertising cookies by visiting:   

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that FlyOrDie is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Requesting access to your personal data

If you wish to review, edit or delete information you have provided to FlyOrDie, you may access your account information under the "Settings" menu on the login page at any time. Under data protection legislation, you have the right to request access to information about you that we hold. To make a request for your personal information, contact [dataprotection@flyordie.com](mailto:dataprotection@flyordie.com)

You also have the right to:

  * object to processing of personal data that is likely to cause, or is causing, damage or distress
  * prevent processing for the purpose of direct marketing
  * object to decisions being taken by automated means
  * in certain circumstances, have inaccurate personal data rectified, blocked, erased or destroyed
  * claim compensation for damages caused by a breach of the Data Protection regulations 

If you have a concern about the way we are collecting or using your personal data, we ask that you raise your concern with us in the first instance.

### Requesting to delete your personal data

You have the right to ask us to delete your personal data at any time. We have the right to refuse the request where we have legal obligations, or legitimate interest to keep them, or we are unable to identify you.

By deleting your account on the game settings page, your personal data will be made unavailable, but they will be kept in order to enable us investigating any illegal or suspicious activities. Your personal data will be deleted one year after being marked for deletion.

By disabling your account (this can be done from the original registration email, when someone else used your email address unauthorised), your personal data will be made unavailable, but they will be kept in order to enable us investigating any illegal or suspicious activities. Your personal data will be deleted one year after being marked for disabling. This will also prevent creating a new account using your email address. Your email address will be stored in an unidentifiable way for this purpose.

### Further information and contact details

Please contact FlyOrDie’s Data Protection Officer if you would like more information on the cookies that we use and their purposes: 

FlyOrDie Data Protection Officer    
10 Kard utca, Gödöllő, 2100 Hungary   
Email: [dataprotection@flyordie.com](mailto:dataprotection@flyordie.com)

Please keep in mind that communication language with FlyOrDie is English regardless of your choice of language in our games. FlyOrDie is not able to process any requests in any other languages.

* * *

## Terms of Service

You may become a member of FlyOrDie by registering on our site. Please read this document carefully before using any FlyOrDie games. By registering to our games and services, you signify you understand, and agree to be bound by, the terms and conditions of its use. If you do not agree to this statement, please do not use our site.

You must be at least 16 years of age to register for use of FlyOrDie.com. 

### Registration

Membership allows you to participate in certain games and activities on FlyOrDie.com. As a FlyOrDie member, you agree to all of the terms and conditions of the Rules of Use and our Privacy Policy, that complement this Agreement. When you accept this Agreement and complete FlyOrDie's registration process, you create a FlyOrDie account and select a login name and password. Your login name should not interfere with our Site Rules above.

Please follow our security guidelines about setting up your account.

You are solely responsible for all activity on your Account and for the security of your computer system. It is important that you do not reveal your password to other users. (If you forget your password, you can request us to send it to the registered email address.) You agree not to reveal your password to other users. Your Account is at risk if you let someone use it inappropriately and your membership is subject to termination if you or anyone using your Account violates our Terms of Service. FlyOrDie reserves the right to restrict access for users who provide unreal data or register multiple Accounts.

### Subscription

You may be a member of FlyOrDie without paying FlyOrDie to participate in a game or other activity.   
You can also subscribe to their premium version to access certain areas of the Service, participate in related activities on [FlyOrDie.com](http://www.flyordie.com/ "Flyordie Online Games"), for a subscription fee which is valid for a given time interval.   
Subscription details are published in the [ Subscription FAQ](http://www.flyordie.com/subscriptionfaq.html). 

FlyOrDie offers a 7-day money back guarantee for the first subscription on your Account. You are NOT eligible for this guarantee if any of your Accounts has been subscribed before, or you have purchased any subscriptions before for any Account on FlyOrDie. Only credit card payments can be refunded under this guarantee. It is FlyOrDie's sole discretion to determine whether you are eligible for this guarantee based on the above. 

FlyOrDie reserves the right to change our fees or billing methods at any time. All changes will be posted on [FlyOrDie.com](http://www.flyordie.com/ "Flyordie Online Games") and you are responsible for reviewing the billing section of FlyOrDie to obtain timely notice of such changes. 

NOTE: Subscription does not mean being exempted from the Rules of Use. 

### Conduct

Please refer to the Rules of Use. If you, or anyone using your Account, violate our online conduct or Content standards, FlyOrDie may take action against your Account. We may issue you a warning about the violation, or we may choose to immediately terminate your Account. You acknowledge that FlyOrDie is not required to provide you notice before terminating your Account, but it may choose to do so.

### Updates

FlyOrDie may update or revise the Membership Agreement at any time. By becoming a Member of FlyOrDie, you agree that FlyOrDie may change the terms of this Membership Agreement. You agree to review the Membership Agreement periodically to become aware of such revisions. You can view the Membership Agreement at any time by clicking on the Terms of Service link at the bottom of our [FlyOrDie.com](http://www.flyordie.com/ "Flyordie Games") home page. Your continued use of the Service after a revised Agreement is posted on FlyOrDie.com will mean that you accept all such revisions. If you don't agree to the changes, or to any of the terms in this Membership Agreement, your only remedy is to cancel your Account (or subscription to a particular area or game). 

### DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES

YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. FLYORDIE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. 

FLYORDIE MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT   
(i) THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS,   
(ii) THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE,   
(iii) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SERVICE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE,   
(iv) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS, AND   
(v) ANY ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE CORRECTED. 

ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL. 

### Indemnity

You agree to indemnify and hold FlyOrDie, and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, co-branders or other partners, and employees, harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of Content you submit, post, transmit or make available through the Service, your use of the Service, your connection to the Service, your violation of the TOS, or your violation of any rights of another. 

### Internet

FlyOrDie assumes no responsibility for any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, or alteration of, entries or transactions. FlyOrDie is not responsible for any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer on-line systems, servers, or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of any e-mail entry or transaction to be received on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any Web site, or any combination thereof, including any injury or damage to participant's or any other person's computer related to or resulting from participation or downloading any materials in this contest. Further FlyOrDie assumes no liability for any losses related to the above outlined failures or caused by any disconnection from the games. 

### Anti-hacking policy

By establishing an account on FlyOrDie, you agree that FlyOrDie is not responsible for any damage, loss, or injury resulting from, hacking, tampering, or other unauthorized access to FlyOrDie or your account. 

Any attempt to gain unauthorized access to FlyOrDie’s systems or any account, interfere with procedures or performance of FlyOrDie, or deliberately damage or undermine FlyOrDie is subject to civil and/or criminal prosecution and will result in immediate termination of your account. 

You must not reverse-engineer, decompile or modify any FlyOrDie client software in any way. You must not use a modified/customised version of the client software or attempt to sub-license it. You must not create or provide any other means by which any FlyOrDie game may be played by others. 

### Account termination

FlyOrDie reserves the right to terminate your account or decline or limit your subscription for any reason, including, but not limited to harassment of other participants, creating multiple accounts, game fraud, or any breach of the terms of the agreement between you and FlyOrDie, and any breach of the security of your account or FlyOrDie.   
Refunds will NOT be given to subscribers who are banned from the site due to violating the Terms of Service (abusive behavior, cheating, etc).   
By registering for an account on FlyOrDie, you consent to allow FlyOrDie to access your account information to investigate complaints or other allegations of abuse. 

Last Update: May 25, 2018.
